http://www.apcon.com/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
APCON.com does not currently support your browser. We will be supporting most browsers soon. If possible, we recommend using the latest versions of Chrome or Firefox to view our site.Thank you for your patience.
Solutions
Core
Network Wide Packet Visibility Enhance Network Security Optimize Network Performance Enable Regulatory Compliance
Industries
Financial Healthcare Government Energy Service Provider Products
Data center
Next-Generation Hybrid VisibilityIntellaView Platform
Scalable Advanced VisibilityIntellaFlex XR Platform
High Speed Packet ProcessingIntellaFlex XR HyperEngine
Packet Aggregation SolutionIntellaFlex XR EdgeSwitch
All-in-One Security & Visibility ApplianceIntellaStore II+
Cloud
AWS VisibilityIntellaCloud
VMware, KVM & Hyper-V Hybrid VisibilityIntellaTap-VM
Management
Hybrid Management Interface IntellaView Management Interface
Multi-Switch Management Titan
Single-Switch ManagementWeb XR
TAPs & Failover
Eliminate Network DowntimeIntellaView Bypass TAP
In-Line Security Tool Failover IntellaFlex Bypass TAPs
Passive Optical Network TAPsAPCON TAPs
Technologies Netflow Generation Network Data De-Duplication Network Latency Measurement Network Packet Filtering Packet Slicing Protocol Header Stripping Tunneling Resources Company Careers About Us News Events Blog Technology Partners Contact Us Partners SupportPrivacy Policy APCON, Inc. is committed to maintaining the trust of our users. This statement explains how we collect information from you and what we do with that information and the circumstances under which we may disclose such information.Information RequestsAPCON offers a variety of resources. For access to some resources on our site, we may ask you to provide some basic contact information. This registration may be for newsletters, events, surveys or other resources.When you choose to download software from the APCON’s support site, your email address and other contact information is required. If you wish to participate in other APCON services or to access free software, manuals, upgrades, and other resources, your email address and other contact information is required.PromotionsUnless you opt out, we may use your information to mail or email promotional materials. We do not sell, trade, rent, share or distribute usernames, E-mail addresses, or registration information to outside organizations not affiliated with or partners with APCON. We may share your information with APCON registered and certified channel partners. Unless we specify differently, our channel partners do not have the rights to use or share the information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist APCON.CookiesWe use common technologies such as cookies and web beacons to keep track of interactions with our website. Cookies are small text files that most websites, including APCON's, place on your computer. Cookies help us identify your interests. They also prevent the need for repeated registration when downloading resources. APCON will not use cookies to track your activities on the web outside of our site. No cookie delivered by us will interfere with the operation of your computer.If you do not want your site usage information collected, you can adjust your browser settings to not accept cookies (if your browser supports this feature).Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our website or in our communications, to help count the number of website visits, or to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.How We Use Your InformationAPCON may use the information you provide to inform you about products, services, or events.We may use your information to help APCON manage, maintain and improve our products, services or website experience.In those instances where our sharing of information is expressly noted at the time you provide it, we may provide that information to those partners specified in the notice. The use of this information by that partner will then be subject to that partner's privacy policies.APCON may share quantitative data gathered from its users, in aggregate form, with others such as advertisers or sponsors. No individual information would be provided in these instances.Every marketing email from APCON has instructions on how to unsubscribe in order to opt out of future mailings.If you have supplied APCON with a telephone number, you may receive telephone calls from us with information about our products and services or events.We do receive information on individual users from our partners. APCON partners have assured us they will notify site users of their intent to collect information. You should review the privacy policies of those partner sites to confirm the way in which they handle their users' information.General ConsiderationsAPCON uses industry-standard best practices, with the goal of keeping your information safe. APCON makes no guarantees regarding the safety of the information you provide to us. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorized persons. There may also be visitors to the site who gather and use the information available there.There may be occasions when APCON is required to provide information in adherence with a court order, or when the law requires that user information be shared or treated as a transferable asset, such as a bankruptcy.APCON Mobile App Privacy PolicyThe next four paragraphs address APCON’s Mobile App privacy policy.Reading Phone StateThe APCON Mobile App reads the mobile device’s phone and network state so as to identify the mobile device’s unique ID. This ID is used by Google Cloud Messaging System to allow notification to be sent to the mobile device from the user’s switch(es) and Titan server.Understanding a Device’s Network LocationsThe APCON Mobile App accesses a mobile device’s location so as to identify the user’s nearest switch closet and Titan server. The switch closet and Titan server are then represented as icons on the APCON Mobile App map.Receiving Alerts and Information – including wake lockAlert and event notifications are sent to APCON Mobile from the user’s switch(es) and/or Titan server.Anything ElseThe APCON Mobile App does not access the user’s voice, video, or photographs on the mobile device.We may revise our privacy policy in the future to adjust to such changes. We recommend that you check it frequently. If you have questions or comments on this Privacy Statement, please ask or submit them by contacting us at info@apcon.com.CareersIf you apply for a job on the APCON careers page, your application and any additional information that you provide will be used to assess your knowledge, skills, and abilities for that position. When you access our application tracking system, you are asked to provide your authorization for APCON to collect, use, process, store, and distribute your personal data as you enter it. In addition, information that you provide will be used for reporting purposes as required by Federal and State laws. We may use your information to communicate with you about career opportunities.
